hey guys rexin here this is the crash
course video to learn changli ASAP so
let's get straight into it without
wasting any time looking at her basic
attack ground combo 1 2 3 4 5 so there's
something to notice here on her fourth
combo she gains a buff called true sight
like this so This icon here it's true
sight for 12 seconds basically means
that her fifth combo is ready at anytime
so you can hold this and press basic
like this it's stored for 12 seconds now
the Nuance here is that true sight can
also be used in the air so I'll show you
the air combo version so jump 1 2 3 four
true sight basic one more
time that is the air version of true
sight this is where it gets technical
because you can mix and match a ground
combo to air combo using the true s side
as well so let me show you what it looks
like so 1 2 3 4 and then for here if you
want to use air true sight press jump
instead of basic attack
jump and then basic to plunge you can
extend that combo in the air instead of
going to plunge by simply waiting for a
bit so 1 2 3 4 true sight jump wait a
bit 1 2 3 4 true sight and then
plunge now the other thing over here is
that once she plunges her ground combo
skips to the third combo instead so you
should get true s even faster after
plunging so 1 2 3 four jump plunge three
four true sight and then basic to finish
or technically speaking you can change
this Forever by using jump combo instead
so 1 2 3 4 jump plunge three four true
sight jump plunge three 4 true sight
jump plunge three 4 you get the idea and
finish with the ground as for her heavy
attack it's a launcher so you saw
earlier that
by doing jump through S side she skips
to the ground basic third combo like
this if you do heavy attack she does the
launch attack and instead it skips to
the third combo of the air attack so
like this heavy attack three 4 5 basic
so that's all you need to know for Chang
Lee in summary she always gets true
sight on the fourth combo so 1 2 3 4
true sight five and then air combo jump
1 2 2 three 4 true sight Air True sight
and then finish with plunge and
everything else is mix and match her
combo to your style either if you want
to do it from ground launching to True
sight and then doing air here or doing a
ground true sight like this that's up to
you so let's move on to her resonance
skill and her forte and her resonance
Liberation so now we'll look at her
skills you already understand that after
every fourth attack she gains true sight
and then when you hit an enemy with true
sight attack she gains one gauge called
inflaman like this so you see down here
I already got one gauge and the
interesting thing about Chang Le is when
she gets a gaaged after the first one
her clothes starts stripping off yes
that's right she starts stripping off
her clothing okay like this I'm going to
show you one more true side I'm just
going to do air one
here right notice how now it's on fire
now let's talk about her resident skill
resonance skill immediately gives her
one stack of uh true sight and then you
can finish finish it off with basic to
get your inflam uh gauge straight away
and it also works as a gap closer so I
can use it at this distance and then
press
e you see that I already got one stack
of uh TR sight and then I can get it
over here get the third gauge and now
more her sleeves are already gone and
then she gets two stacks of Resident
skill I'm going to use the second one
that and then just finish it off with
another true sight and she already has
full Stacks now so what you do when
there's full Stacks simply press and
whole basic to do her heavy attack like
[Music]
that so that's her forte circuit so to
recap again two stacks of uh resonance
skill every time has their own cool down
like
that and then you get true sight use it
and do it again you get true sight use
it so that's two stacks easily two
stacks of inflaman and the other two you
just need to get it yourself by either
doing combo
or her intro attack her intro attack
also gives her true
sight and then once you have full gauge
press and whole basic like
that just like that as for her resonance
Liberation her ultimate it gives her
four stacks of inflam immediately so you
press
ultimate and then notice I have four
Stacks straight away so the combo is to
do ultimate and immediately press and
hold basic attack to do her
forte that's the combo for ultimate so
changli is pretty simple to play as far
as rotation go just get four of inflaman
stacks via true sight you can get two
easily from Resident skill true sight
and then another two more one from your
own combo one from intro attack and then
do heavy attack and then when ultimate
is ready do ultimate and then do heavy
attack once more there is also a fun
aesthetic thing here where when she has
four stacks and you press ultimate along
with it her blindfold is going to get
burned alongside in the animation like
[Music]
so it looks really cool however if you
want to talk about efficiency you don't
want to do that because you need the
four stacks on to have that blindfold
and when you have four stacks and then
you do ultimate you waste you're
essentially wasting four whole stacks of
inflaman with the ultimate so the best
is always to clear your your stacks and
then use ultimate for four more stacks
and then use heavy attack to clear all
the stacks again and that's pretty much
it for Changi so let's look at her
skills over here quickly on her intro
attack intro gives her true sight so
I'll show you what her rotation
generally looks like there's no hard and
fast way to do this as long as you do
the intro and then one normal chain and
then two resonance skills so I'll start
off with Verina get an outro so I'm
going to switch Chang Le in do her intro
attack that will give her one stack and
then finish one normal basic attack
combo to get the second stack and then
press resonance skill basic attack to
get third stack resonance skill again
basic attack to get the fourth stack
heavy attack to spend all the gauge and
then use ultimate and then heavy attack
again to spend all the gauge so let's
begin Chung Le go
in ground
[Music]
attack that's the second one press
resident skill basic attack third one
resident skill basic attack fourth one
heavy attack
ultimate and then heavy attack one more
time and that's it that's Chang Le's
rotation when she switches
in pretty simple
right so we'll go through her skills
we've already explained most of them on
field normal
attack simple and then resonance skill
resonance skill grants true sight for 12
seconds and then for Forte circuit it's
basically the one where she B holds
basic attack when she has four Stacks
flaming sacrifice so this is the attack
and we already know this to get inflaman
which is the gauge stack after using her
basic attack true side Conquest that's
the ground one or true side charge
that's the Phenix one she always gets
one stack and ultimate gives her four
Stacks straight away her intro also
gives her one stack for her ultimate and
additional thing to know is that after
using ultimate she gets this buff called
fiery feather buff within 10 seconds
when she uses her heavy attack with full
gauge the attack is increased by 25% for
it that's why after ultimate always make
sure to use heavy attack right after it
within 10 seconds for this extra damage
and intro skill we already know this
intro skill she gets true sight and for
her first inherent skill she gets a
fusion damage bonus increased by 5% for
each stack of inflam she has but this
only Buffs true sight conquest and true
sight charge true sight Conquest is the
fifth basic attack on the ground true
sight charge is the air basic attack
which is the Phoenix and inherent skill
is the really good one whenever she does
a forte flaming sacrifice which is the
whole basic with full gauge or her
ultimate her Fusion damage is increased
by 20% and she ignores 15% of the
target's defense so that's basically it
for Chang Le's Forte as for her weapon
if you don't have any of the five star
weapon you can use either Luna cutter or
Commando of conviction if you have the
five star star weapons Emerald Genesis
is really good if you selected this
weapon from your f2p festar weapon box
or if you can go want to go all the way
you can get blazing Brilliance her own
weapon it also looks really good right
aesthetically pleasing and depending on
the weapon Emerald Genesis has crit rate
main stat and blazing Brilliance is crit
damage main stat so we'll go over to her
Echo so the stats that you need to look
out for for Echo for the for cost for
the main stat obviously if your weapon
is already crit rate you can top off the
rest of the crit rate from substats and
you can afford to put crit damage here
for her for cost Echo otherwise if
you're already using her main weapon
blazing brillians over here you can go
for crit rate to supplement more crit
rate just like my build here as for
substats to look out for it's the usual
you want to look out for both crit rate
crit damage resonance skill especially
most of Tang Le's attacks scale of
resonance skill energy and attack
percent as for a resonance chain S1 it
gives super armor when she does her
resonance skill and heavy attack with
the full gauge and also increase the
damage dealt by 10% S2 is the one where
you can actually change your build
around it S2 Straight Up gives her crit
rate by 25% as long as she has a gauge
point and flam so having this crit rate
25% even if you're using blazing
Brilliance which gives crit damage you
can also afford to go crit damage over
here on Inferno Rider if you're
confident in getting crit rate sub stats
on all your Echo so that's something to
consider as for S3 3 Ultimate damage
increased by 80% really straightforward
so S2 to S3 I would say is the best uh
stopping point for most people S4 is
supportive after using intro attack of
everyone increase by 20% for 30 seconds
and S5 is pretty massive heavy attack
flaming sacrifice which is the heavy
attack with full gauge multiplier is
increased by 50% and damage dealt is
also increased by 50% so this is massive
if you're going to wail for her S6 adds
even more defense ignore to her
resonance skill her heavy attack with
full gauge and her resonance Liberation
additional 40% of Target defense ignore
so that's pretty much it for changli as
for team building team building so far
in withering waves is really simple your
first character that you bring in is
always the Healer the one that's
carrying the healing set so of course
Vina is the best in slot if you don't
have Vina you can use B like this so
either b or Vina always and then for
Chang Le's outro changli gives Fusion
damage and resonance Liberation 20% and
25% respectively for 10 seconds to the
next character so changli can function
both as a main DPS or a second DPS sub
DPS or the third character so it's
really flexible it you can go Vina
Changi and then you put susia here so
the sequence goes like this Vina comes
in buff everyone Changi comes in outro
buff into tsia and tsia just does all
her nuke you can also do the quick swap
method by simply just swapping between
the both of them as the main DPS or if
you want Changi to be the main DPS you
can can also put for example yangyang
here since Chang Le has a really high uh
energy requirement yangyang will give
Ultimate Energy charge over time for
changli so this is like the comfy build
for changli in my opinion otherwise you
can also do this similar to tisia build
you can also put Encore and then you
quick swap between them all the time
since Changi also Buffs resonance
Liberation you can also put Changi here
and then put Havoc Rover here I don't
have him switched to Havoc right now but
if you put Havoc Rover here Chung Le's
rooll Works uh the same as yinlin before
the same build Yin Lin also Buffs
resonance Liberation you can put
changling here and then switch Rover in
have a Grover for that big Ultimate N so
yeah pretty flexible all around and
that's all you need to know for changli
this is the crash course so yeah in my
opinion changle is one of the most fun
melee characters so far she has so much
Gap closing especially in her basic
attack like this true s side and then
she just teleports to them even her e
skill just teleports to them and then
you get true side again and you get to
teleport to them
again really
fun even for f2p her damage is
respectable see like this and then just
[Music]
ultimate and then
heavy and that guy over there e
skill so really mobile really satisfying
so many hits to her skill easy parrying
with that many hits so yeah that
concludes the Chung Le crash course
guide I hope that it's been helpful to
you in understanding her move set
consider leaving a like subscribe to my
channel and I'll see you in the next
video I've also made a chungi styling
video over here that you can check it
out and one last thing is that chungi
only needs one hit to Min a
rock op all right see you guys bye-bye